Base to Mars I got Mars water, yes sir I
drank it just now Sir did you get water on Mars
and you drank it No no sir I brought it in a bottle with me, I
drank it when the remand on ICICI Lord Oil Take Care App came It is
for buying and renewing insurance policy, but there is a
lot of things with it, nothing at all
Sir its face can track your vitals You can
also get doctor consultation You can
also chat with experts for diet This app
is out of the world Sir tell me can this app
stop my hair fall Hello hello hello
Bad network Sir you
get so many features with insurance, so ICICI
Lord Oil Take Care App is out of this
world, isn't it? Lord Oil Take
Care App is out of this world